: Mr. Director?
: Where are we going?
: Oh, don’t worry Wilty.
: It’s a… surprise.
: Oh boy, oh boy! A surprise?
: Just for me??
: Oh I can't wait!
: Don’t worry, Wilty.
: We'll be there soon.
[color:#777777](Elevator stops)
[color:#777777](Elevator door opens)
[color:#777777](Walking sounds)
: Mr. Director, why are we back on set?
: I thought production was c-c-canceled t-today?
: Do you remember that little "stunt" you pulled yesterday?
: The one where you started crying, live on set.
: Y- Yes s-sir...
: Do you remember how we had to DRAG you OFF SET just so the kid would STOP CRYING!?
: Do you remember how you KICKED and SCREAMED while Kris watched their CHILDHOOD HERO act like SUCH, A, WIMP!?
: Tch… I expected better from you.
: I- I’m s-s-sorry, Mr-
: A SORRY, Isn’t going to CUT IT.
: Now, you’re going to walk on set, and you’re gonna record another episode, GOT IT?
: Yes sir…
: Good.
[color:#777777](Walking sounds)
: I’m sorry I have to do this, old friend…
: But you did this to yourself...
: Goodbye.
: Director, Wait!!!
[color:#777777](Elevator door closes)