: …D-Dear diary.
: I.. don’t know what day’s it is..
: I-it’s all blurring together.
: It- It’s been… ssso long, too long.
: I’ve been so alone.
: I feel like I’ve been’s hearing things…
: The mirrors’s are talking to me, the walls.
: Everything.
: I feel’s like I’ve been’s seeing faces.
:  Familiar ones, ones like-
: I DON'T EVEN WANNA SAY HIS NAME!
: I… I still don’t understand why he DID THAT!
: surely what I did’s wasn’t THAT bad in his eyes! ...right?
: Gosh I, I miss Kris.
: Being able to entertain them’s,
: put a smile on their face…
: What went’s wrong?
: I feel like I always say something about’s that in every one of these.
: I just... I just wish’s I wasn’t so alone’s!
: I wish I’s could turn’s back the clock,
: back’s to the good old’s days.
: …What’s the point’s in even making these?
: Nobody’s gonna find them's!
: NOBODY will come! not here… not ever.
[color:#777777](Sigh)
[color:#777777](Walking sounds)
: Look at yourself.
: You look’s horrible.
: A shell’s of what could’ve been’s.
[color:#777777](Mysterious noise)
: Huh?
[color:#777777](Item collected)
: What's this?
: My skin’s! it- It’s m-m-moving's!
[color:#777777](Snapping and screaming)
: W- What’s hap-p-p-pening to mmMME!?
: I- I feel… I feel’s…
: ha-hAHAHA-HAHA
: I FEEL'S WONDERFUL!!!
: HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAhaHahaAhAHAHa